She really left
It's not that she didn't look back
She is completely done looking back
Chengze
Regarding what happened today
The Gu family owes
the Su family an explanation
I'll explain
Uncle Su
But let me bring her back first
Mr Fu you're quite considerate
Professional habit
Protecting my employer
You're not just my employer now
Su Mingyao
are you really leaving with him
Didn't you just see it
Heh he's just a bodyguard
What do you see in him
Watch your tone Young Master Gu
It's not your place to
tell me how to talk to him
He just chose me
So it is my place
I'll give you one last chance
I don't need it
Go back now and
explain the recording
as a misunderstanding
I can let this slide
I'm the one you publicly broke off
the engagement with
and now I have to sign a statement too